<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Moh. Zulkifli Katili</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Moh. Zulkifli Katili</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kikiraihan.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Panah Papua: Mapping the Sago Forest of West Papua</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/panah-papua/</link><pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/panah-papua/</guid><description>Panah Papua: Mapping the Sago Forest of West Papua 🔗 web-URL: website link ⏱️ Project Duration: 2 weeks Brief : Panah Papua is a non-governmental organization dedicated to the preservation of Papuan traditional land and forests. As an association of Papuan traditional land and forest fighters, Panah Papua aims to protect and sustainably manage the rich biodiversity of the Sago Forest in West Papua, Indonesia. They require a software engineer and spatial data analyst to develop a map page and spatial data system for the Papuan Sago Forest.</description></item><item><title>IPB Summer Course Project: Advancing Smart Agriculture with Machine Learning</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/ipb-summer-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/ipb-summer-2023/</guid><description>IPB Summer Course Project: Advancing Smart Agriculture with Machine Learning 🔗 URL: About Course ⏱️ Working Period: 8–20 October 2023 Overview: The International Summer Course of AI and Optimization for Smart Agriculture and Biomedical Applications held at IPB in October 2023 provided a platform for interdisciplinary collaboration and innovation in the field of data science and artificial intelligence (AI). As a Machine Learning Engineer, I spearheaded a project focused on clustering melon leaf images using advanced algorithms, contributing to the advancement of smart agriculture practices.</description></item><item><title>PT. MAKASSAR RAYA MOTOR: Optimizing Sales Strategies through Spatial Analysis</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/mrm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 01 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/mrm/</guid><description>PT. MAKASSAR RAYA MOTOR: Optimizing Sales Strategies through Spatial Analysis 🔗 URL: Client Profile ⏱️ Working Period: October 2023 - June 2024 Brief : PT. Makassar Raya Motor is a prominent Daihatsu dealer company based in Makassar, Indonesia, with a strong presence across South Sulawesi, Central Sulawesi, and Southeast Sulawesi. With 10 branches strategically located across these provinces, the company sought to enhance its sales strategies through data-driven insights. As a Software Engineer &amp;amp; Data Analyst under contract, our role was pivotal in conducting spatial analysis of sales data and developing a comprehensive dashboard to visualize key metrics.</description></item><item><title>Contag School: Revolutionizing University Academic Affairs Management</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/contag/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/contag/</guid><description>Contag School: Revolutionizing University Academic Affairs Management 🔗 URL: Startup Profile ⏱️ Working Period: March 2023 - October 2023 Brief : During our engagement with Contag School, we focused on delivering robust backend solutions to support their SaaS products. The following highlights summarize our contributions:
Solution : During our engagement with Contag School, we focused on delivering robust backend solutions to support their SaaS products. The following highlights summarize our contributions:</description></item><item><title>VektorPedia: Insect Vector Search Engine (Master Thesis)</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/vektorpedia/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Aug 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/vektorpedia/</guid><description>VektorPedia: Insect Vector Search Engine (Master Thesis) 🔗 URL: vektorpedia.ipb.ac.id Paper Published. ⏱️ Working Period: August 2022 - December 2023 Overview: This project, conducted under the guidance of a supervisor as part of my master&amp;rsquo;s thesis, focused on creating a search engine named VektorPedia for identifying insects that carry plant viruses. By leveraging the power of knowledge graphs (KGs) and the latest advancements in data representation, we aimed to enhance the understanding and management of biodiversity information.</description></item><item><title>Anak-anak di Masjid Umar Bin Khattab Bypass</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/blogs/pertama/</link><pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2022 22:57:33 +0800</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/blogs/pertama/</guid><description>Kami baru saja selesai melaksanakan sholat jum&amp;rsquo;at di masjid umar bin khattab bypass. Kami duduk sejenak untuk bersantai, menunggu awan melintas dilangit untuk melindungi kami dari terik matahari gorontalo yang saking panasnya, konon katanya disini mataharinya dua wkwk.
Kami lalu dikagetkan dengan aktivitas anak kecil disekeliling kami. Awalnya saya pikir mereka sedang bermain, namun ternyata mereka sedang membantu merapikan karpet masjid selesai dipakai jamaah sholat. Saya melihat senyum berseri dari wajah kecil mereka, ketika diberikan uang 2000 rupiah oleh bapak takmirul.</description></item><item><title>Digimosque : making API and admin panels for digital mosque</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/digimosque/</link><pubDate>Fri, 06 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/digimosque/</guid><description>Digimosque: making API and admin panels for digital mosque android applications&amp;quot; 🔗 URL: Startup Profile Brief : Digimosque is a startup that carries a digital mosque platform that can make it easier to find information on mosques in the area and also as a place to make donations for religious activities. This application provides information on mosques around us, takmir features for cash/infaq/qurban management etc., IOT tools (monitors, air conditioners, prayer times, etc.</description></item><item><title>Jadwalin : Course Schedule Management System</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/pembimbing_sisa/</link><pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/pembimbing_sisa/</guid><description>Jadwalin Brief : The Faculty of Islamic Economics and Business, IAIN Sultan Amai Gorontalo, requires a system to manage course schedules on a faculty scale. Available course data and sample schedules are in the form of excell files, which are obtained from the Academic Information System (SIAK). In this case, access through the SIAK API is not permitted for certain reasons. The system must consider:
Department → the schedule for students in one major may not collide.</description></item><item><title>TimeMarket : Workload Management Application</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/timemarket/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/timemarket/</guid><description>TimeMarket Brief : Workload management applications such as human resource management are needed to be included in the BI Innovation program. The application aims to facilitate the delegation of work accurately, for the purpose of efficiency in managing and monitoring employee work, as well as limiting the number of employee jobs that are considered reasonable. Applications must be accessible from anywhere, and easy to use.
Working time : 2 months (tetantive) + maintenance</description></item><item><title>Sindasi: Student Recommended SPK Using the AHP-TOPSIS Method</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/sindasi/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/sindasi/</guid><description>Sindasi: Student Recommended SPK Using the AHP-TOPSIS Method Brief : An application is needed that can assist the Department Bureaucracy in finding suitable students for certain cases such as competitions/research etc. The application must be dynamic, meaning that it can be adjusted, so that it can be used in multiple cases as long as it uses student data (Courses scores, organization, parents&amp;rsquo; salaries) in the form of information filled in by the student as well as course grade data from an academic information system.</description></item><item><title>Kongkong : Students Crowdfunding Platform</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/kongkong/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/projects/kongkong/</guid><description>Kongkong Student Crowdfunding Platform (Practice Project) Brief : We plan to develop a crowdfunding platform for student activities, the idea is to provide an alternative source of funding for students who want to carry out activities instead of having to run a list of funds per person, without explaining activity information.
My task is to make the appearance of the application match the target student user. It takes a display that is flexible as well as responsive.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Social Email: mohzulkiflikatili@gmail.com Phone/WA: +628-229150-1085 Linkedin: Moh Zulkifli Katili Facebook: Moh Zulkifli Katili Twitter: @inikikikatili Instagram: @inikikikatili Github: @kikiraihan Address No.20, Sawah Besar Street
Bone Bolango District
Indonesia</description></item><item><title>Resume</title><link>https://kikiraihan.github.io/resume/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kikiraihan.github.io/resume/</guid><description>👋🏼 Hello, I am Mohammad Zulkifli Katili (Kiki). a Data-Driven Software Developer adept in Python, PHP, JavaScript, SQL, NoSQL, RDF-SPARQL, and SAP Analytic. Excels in software development, machine learning, graph analytics, and data analysis. Passionate about leveraging tech for impactful solutions. A Teamwork person, with a strong desire to work with a team to achieve common goals.
🎓 Education 2021-Now | IPB University Link Computer Science Master&amp;rsquo;s Program, in Computational Intelegence and Optimization Division (GPA : 3.</description></item></channel></rss>